good money Twitter and YouTube I'm just
gonna go over to my Twitter and the link
to participate in place where I can put
it in the comments of the livestream
there we go good lord it's a bait on or
help if I can
can Lola we go and the end the youtube
comment in the youtube aurora my love
you
my kid has a new gig that she downloaded
that is one of her one of the ones that
I'm not not a fan of their marketing
strategies to say the least
so choose your own religion that is
today's topic
yesterday's will make a rule
conversation was amazing and we spent
the half an hour beforehand with two of
the people talking about these four
questions that I keep sitting with now
five questions we have added a question
that's the central question because they
correspond with someone else's idea for
more of how things get built in the
world and I never remember his five five
things RL a word it's like code build
learn burn is one of them and I don't
remember the fifth one but the
definition or not the definition of a
religion to me the one of the biggest
problems with religion isn't that people
believe anything it's that they require
everybody else to believe it you believe
that that Jesus came back and died for
your sins not a problem that you need
everybody else to believe that Jesus
came back and died for your sins so we
can live under a Christian governments
problem that you're you know Hindu and
believe in that everything is God and
believe in Krishna and not a problem
that you don't want Muslims in your
country problem right that you that
they're not allowed to be here if they
believe in Mohammed as their what is
Muhammad Prophet as their prophet and
yes problem hi so could we have a
religion that truly sees the individual
allows them to follow their own path yet
connects us because religions also give
us that right they give us a sense of
connection and togetherness that we all
do believe in that that's what what
defines us to give us generally a place
to worship
a place to fulfill that purpose and
they give us that's like I do I wrote
this down somewhere
they give us meaning religion gives us a
meaning belonging and a purpose to life
the Church of the Flying Spaghetti
Monster yeah exactly
finding a path that we can all follow
that does actually unite us is something
that can't come from one central person
or else you're United around a new
central person which is by definition a
cult and not a which is just really a
smaller religion that's kind of our
definition on this in this on this
planet of a cult Birch's of religion is
a religion is like big enough we've
given you state funding we've given you
state funding but that you're allowed to
get get donations and they're considered
tax-exempt a cults being really just a
mini of any religion but these these
five questions as well as the how we're
gonna be exploring them couldn't get
past it on Friday
yeah problem people other people are
stocking up just for them is that what
they just eat past on Friday I'm not
actually familiar with spaghetti monster
despite the fact that many of people
many a person bring it up as they're
like basically atheist religion but to
not have that right not have a farce
pretend religion but when it actually
speaks to people's hearts and souls that
isn't about worshiping a deity even if
that is an individual part for some
people right so you'll believe in God
smoke believe in the God of the Bible or
the God of the Torah which same God but
you know um gone to the cron all same
God
his little eNOS was not pleased despite
you it's a noodle eNOS can see like
spaghetti monster religion is one of my
favorites for sure because of all the
wonderful puns
even though normally I hate puns there's
something about the fluence of any
monster but if we can each answer these
five questions other people answering
them in their own way it doesn't take
away from us answering them and vice
versa in fact if anything and helping
other people answer them it's gonna help
them I grew up
an evangelical Christian I'm just gonna
say Church and really it was church is
so evangelical Christian churches and
the amount of hypocrisy the amount of
like Sunday Christians whether it's just
like higher than thou dirt on Sunday and
go back to your hedonist ways every
other day or just like I'm the gateway
to God and you you're not worthy because
you don't meet up to my standards even
if they're not clergy they're just you
know a random person in the congregation
that sees themselves as higher or other
people see as higher and I don't think
there's actual truth to that I don't
think anyone is higher closer but these
five questions that I am figuring out
how we can explore together without
there being a central authority right
without it being in any way I am the
Gateway to these five questions because
I'm not your the gateway to these five
questions right I can't answer for
anyone who are you who are your people
what is your purpose what do you need
and now the fifth question what are you
willing to let go of what are you ready
to get let go of within all of those
four right what do you actually need and
not need what do you but at any level
that people answer Who am I they have
more of themselves to show up with and
be seen and accepted in a group the more
people are able to find their group of
people whether that has anything to do
with a spiritual purpose or just a
common a common mission a common verb
common right you're all we're all
playing basketball we're all cleaning up
this riverbed whatever the actual common
common healthy between that is how
peanut one string a sentence together
thirty thirty one morning
whatever the commonality is these five
questions but just if we can build
something that actually gets people
closer to their version of religion
their version of whatever it ignites
their soul and helps them feel closer
and that is one of the questions I've
written down here that was going to be
the questions how to choose your own
religion but I felt she's your own
religion got the point across of when do
you feel
connected to source or God or the
universe whatever word you use for it
when does that happen for you and how
can we facilitate it for each other so I
don't need to dictate to anybody when
you should feel closer to source to God
at the universe I we could facilitate
helping people find that I told this
story a few times but when I was on back
when the pandemic wasn't on and we were
actually cooking together as community I
was with one of the people in the
community who is he's very Christian and
we're talking about and he was
administer at church he now works in the
in the food sovereignty part of the
church but still is very it's his
purpose in life right to be to be
intertwined with with the church and I
was saying how my version of church if I
could find it what is singing out in
nature at one time I was taking his
permaculture course and the Woodward
singers that I've sang with before but
not regularly were like singing in this
garden we were repeating what was sung
and we were walking around and it was
just this way this is one this is church
this is what I want this is what I want
is what rejuvenates my soul and helps
they feel more connected and the closest
thing I have to that which I do do is I
go for walks and air saying to myself
constantly I mean it look like a crazy
person
but it feels good and I it feels better
than looking I don't care what the load
side world necessarily thinks of me most
of the time obviously I feel a little
worse now that my kid goes to the local
school classmates families that I'm
walking past will see into myself but I
it brings more happiness than it brings
problem finding that peace that ignites
your soul and being able to facilitate
oh sorry the point of the story that I
didn't finish was that this guy was then
like oh yeah my friend does that my
friend a host different a singing
session I believe was every Sunday in a
different piece of nature around the
Lower Mainland I was like what this
already exists but I know about it until
having this conversation I also had like
a
four years ago now can't even four years
ago let's say three years ago sure
around this time I had a roommate move
in with me who was under undergoing
participating in Ramadan and for the
first time I saw somebody truly like
intimately participate in Ramadan and I
hadn't seen it before and I was like
what a beautiful ceremony like just that
this entire religion takes on feeling
weaker and less than for however many
days so that they can understand what
it's like to be in poverty and be sick
and she was away from her extended
family which was hard she wasn't with
her kids she wasn't with her her
siblings and her parents and it is also
a very community food based cultural
event
and watching her go through that alone
cuz I mean I couldn't really piss I'm
not gonna participate in robbing I'm not
gonna not eat during the day I can
celebrate with you after sundown it was
also in Canada during the winter
solstice so it's like the most time
unless you're up north basically the
most time you could go without eating
because it's from sunup to sundown and
more time after that anyway but what is
the problem when she moved in because
she had just moved to Vancouver she
couldn't find a mosque that that was in
alignment with her like she was
questioning her religion she wanted to
talk to an imam who could understand
that and help her through her her moment
of crisis and she couldn't find it and I
have parents and family who are who are
a mom I have a mom who's religious and
family in general who's religious and
anytime they go to a new place they like
come visit Vancouver or just like I
don't know how many churches i mother's
been to in Alberta but many many a
church like how even from that
standpoint right from if you're one of
the big religions that are considered
religions how do you find your place of
worship how do you find the place like
what is even in a Christian Church which
is what I grew up with there are so many
variables that
um make a church feel like home or make
a church feel like it resonates with you
for me it's funny because I keep going
to try and to like recreate my childhood
experience like fer nostalgia and the
truth is every different church Saints
different song so it's never gonna
really resonate there's like a couple
that are sung more commonly throughout
the churches but very few most of them
were very specific to that church it was
like the minister's wife wrote them or
something along those lines so I don't
get my nostalgia I can't and I don't
want to just go sing about God I wanted
to hear the songs that I say as a child
but God and finding and then this is
just gonna become time I more recently
with my child feeling like I was missing
out on not the church because I never
wanted to go back to the church but like
that community an intergenerational
community that I was participating as a
kid that I got a lot out of even if I
also paid a lot of price for it that I
wanted that and so I went to the United
Unitarian let's say United the United
Church the one that's like basically I
don't even mention God and religion wise
really resonates with me but the actual
service I was like this is boring like
this guy isn't preparing it like it's I
don't know there wasn't like the fire
and they're like these were subjects
that I wanted to talk about like one of
them was I don't know something to do
with indigenous rights and environment
and all and I'm like and it's boring so
why am I so and then the songs weren't
lively and fun they were like him in
oils that don't mention God it was like
you're not doing good sermons and you're
not singing good it's not I don't want
to sing these songs and so it doesn't
resonate with me I want I want songs in
nature and I want good intellectual
conversation actually even more so than
I I don't actually want to serve Him in
all honesty but there's also so more
recently I learned about the Quakers
this woman on YouTube I came over her
name Jessica I don't remember and she
has a wife and then a nice name is that
our wives really attracted actually both
really attractive just Jessica's not my
style not the point
she was talked with hot she's a Quaker
and talked about what a Quaker is
and her entire thing about I was like
how did I not know about this Quakers
are I think they believed in the Bible
but they go to church and their church
service they might call it something
different is like the kids go off to
Sunday school and the adults stay in a
room and they like I think they walk
around may be seated but walking around
in silence until someone feels the need
to speak and then they speak and
sometimes it's related to the last
person speaking you don't prepare
something ahead of time it's about the
moment and allowing it to return so it's
basically like a group meditation it's
also this conversation that comes up
hello dr. kids and so having I was like
how did I not hear about this why am I
not a Quaker and it's because Quakers
don't proselytize they don't go out and
ask people to come to their church they
don't go out and be like this would
really resonate with you and there's
something about like the religions that
really should shut the up are the
ones that are out knocking on everyone's
door and being like have you heard
you're going to hell if you don't listen
to us and those that actually could help
people and meet people where they at
don't know how to market like is broken
this broken piece cause I'm like
Quakerism sounds like the world could
need it the world a group meditation you
can kind of believe that anything would
be part of this and it's called Quakers
so I I was expecting I grew up in like
Amish country but hunter a country and
that's what like Quakers were with me it
was like old-fashioned that and I knew
that they were peaceful but not I did
not the part I was like you're a Quaker
really oh I love Jessica Jessica's got
several disabilities but every time
she's on camera
she's looked like she looks like a 60s
50s 50s 60s housewife like decked out to
the nines of these beautiful dresses and
she talks with it she's British so put
the British accent and then I don't I
don't know if her wife is four - action
wave might be American I don't know I
remember hearing her talk about do not
equate religion that being able to pick
and choose what it is that feeds our
soul be able to find the space that
works for us so like if there is a
church
and you want it to have XY and Z I don't
think what I what I want in a church
actually exists because I need it not to
mention God but have worship like so
he's like God like this does not it
doesn't exist
but singing out in nature does and being
able to just know that exist and be able
to find out how I get there when it's
happening would be amazing being able to
offer everybody that not everybody see
is gonna be seen in nature that's not
the new religion that's not it's my
piece of it right it's like what I want
to do to feel my soul what can I do and
so to be able to have literally a build
your own religion website where it's
like okay what what what practices do
you want to put together here's all the
practices that exist what do you want to
put together
is there a congregation or whatever you
want to code up or you want to call it
whatever your religion calls it in your
area and how do we help you assess
whether it's right for you or not the
size the service timing be close to your
place the actual religion should
probably be in alignment this works on
all levels
it's a Sikh temple perfect actually that
sounds great having the ability to come
together under the umbrella of not
having an umbrella but these five
questions there's something about them
that I'm like they're there they are
their own non answering them is your
personal religion like it's your
personal spiritual practice that you
never fully answer nobody cancer them
for you even if people can help right
there is no preacher that can give you
these answers there's only people who've
been through this process you can be
like yes this is what I did and what
worked for me and if you're somebody
that the majority of things work for the
work for other people you follow the
majority and if you're someone who like
me and the majority of things don't work
for you you find your niche you find the
pieces that do work for you and like I
don't need people who I'm singing in
nature with to believe every tenant that
I believe in
but chances about or next to zero I need
them to show up and want to sing the
same songs together in the same location
right so there's whereas of course if
you're in a Catholic Church you're gonna
want everyone to follow the Catholic
religion and you're gonna want people to
be under under that but then how under
that do you need to be you need to
believe in a hundred percent a hundred
percent as deeply as everybody else or
can you believe in ninety percent of it
you believe an eighty percent of it but
that's not the point where I'm answering
the metric so you want to move legend
but that might be something that you
care about right if you're Catholic
you're raised Catholic you still
identify as Catholic but you also only
ninety percent resonate with it
which church works for you which one
actually would would follow um would you
want to be part of and so basically I'm
talking about two different platforms
one of which is find your worshiping
Center find your community which comes
under the fifth question where my people
who and where are my people right if
you're cast like your people are
Catholic under the religion umbrella
your people also might be your
profession and your everything else
every other category that were part of
but finding helping people find their
place of worship also helps them unfine
it if you feel so tied to your by the
way I'm paralyzed is interrupting me at
this exact moment time but if you want
to join me on camera and answer these
questions or talk about your religious
experience how you find it found your
religion unique amongst amongst the many
born into it so is just less interesting
because you didn't really have to fight
for it but what what did what drew you
in and where you find especially where
what ignites your heart and soul which
my own personal issue the shadow side
I'm not really interested in hearing
about I found God and God is the answer
to everything
I'm interested in why God's the answer
and everything for you but God is an SL
the answer to everything everything for
everyone and that is to me what if we're
gonna find a common religion if we're
going to be able to get along with
different religions because no one's
ever gonna be a burn unless we murder
everyone who's not we're never gonna
have everyone be Christian everyone be
Muslim everyone be seek and so how we
get along on this planet well we're
different is a big part of like to you
choose your own you choose which one
resonates with you including none of the
above right including all of the above
that to me my religion is picking and
choosing it's picking and choosing the
practices and the people and the things
that I like none of the religions but
out of a lot of B M C cultural practices
my religions cultural appropriation it
turns out but no it's not it's a but
yeah I mean I I if something resonates
deep down but Society says not to do it
I listen more to my inner soul than I do
to society and so part of that is actual
culture appropriation it's like me and
my god tell me I was to use it but this
group of people say I'm not supposed to
use it who do I listen to
who has the right who doesn't have the
right that's its own like um a lot of
people and I understand and I even
slightly agree and yet don't agree well
my life explained is that like part of
the reason people cling to like African
American culture especially or First
Nations culture is they don't really
have one of their own
and so the key is to go back to your own
heritage and look at what you what your
people did and like for my people like
you know many people are in me which one
do I get to pick and choose now can I
choose first nation with seven minute
I'm head up a bit of Cherokee
can I pick Judaism in fact I know
nothing about it cuz I've one Jewish
grandparent like yeah I'm allowed to
pick those but I'm not allowed to pick
African because that one actually like
the continent Africa resonates with me
and it's a little what which one am I
allowed to which one am I not allowed to
which what am I allowed to do and not
allowed to do and to me it has to be
does it resonate with me like I love
yoga yoga feels good for my body and my
soul and so I do it um luckily it comes
from one of the cultures that actually
is kind of pro cultures like yeah it
works for you use it but not
everyone there feels that way he didn't
take a poll it's not everyone but I
wasn't using sponging because I didn't
believe in it until someone introduced
me to it and now I smudge it's like okay
that's actually the key to me do I
believe in it do I think it's a thing
because if I believe yoga works which is
why I don't think it belongs to a
certain group of people if it makes your
body feel better if it connects you to
the earth it works
like what whereas I didn't believe in
smudging until I did and then it was
like well if it kills bad bacteria if it
actually cleanses a space then who's who
gets that and who doesn't get that and
so it's it's whatever that's that's my
own my own issue of like well I don't
want to go back and learn my Celtic
roots I don't that's not what connects
me that's not what I feel drawn to and
in fact I feel anti drawn to anything
that's around a central figure I don't
care how awesome that central figure is
and all tribal that I know of have
hierarchical central figures have even
if they're less close anyway no point
building our own religion and how
talking about two different platforms
that are coming up in my head is one of
which is find your congregation find
your place of worship and it can be an a
single event it can be things like
singing in nature who do you need to be
to be included maybe they're singing
hymn in a song therefore I'm not gonna
want to go maybe it's more call and
respond like Woodward singers and
sometimes that resonates with me and
sometimes it doesn't and so finding your
place and the other thing is literally a
site that can help you build your own
religion like if we think more about a
site that it guess helps you on a
journey to happiness
so which in and of itself is kind of its
own religion but not again there's no
central figure there is no like it's
what I look up just do that now since
owens joining me looking up like what
what it is to be a cult and if we can do
the opposite of that exact opposite of
what it is to be a cult and which is
basically like everyone on the outside
is bad and we're good
no everyone's worthy everyone is worthy
you know I don't I don't get to decide
on your word
it's already been decided you're worthy
and so you're not living by my standards
it doesn't make you less worthy me not
love you by my own standards I can
decide my own self-worth is maybe less
than even if that's not the truth but
finding a way to answer these questions
or any questions that do resonate with
with a broader group of people I mean
like how you found God is not only it's
not on this list right it's because even
that word even the word God when I use
it I don't use that word because it
doesn't resonate well with me I use the
word universe and more recently at least
on this last source it is the source of
everything what do you call it I don't
know but I think of God is the person in
the Old and New Testament and it does
not resonate with me but finding a way
to create your meaning in your life and
your access to happiness whether you
want to call that a religion or not
because again more religion clearly has
got a date with people but if you can
find tools and practices to help you
figure out who you are at a deeper and
deeper level or more surface and more
surface level I mean part of what we
were talking about yesterday was how to
explore that and talking about like the
fun questions to ask that are less Who
am I is a pretty serious profound
question whereas like if I was a
vegetable which vegetable would I be is
fun and playful and not it tells you a
lot about yourself
possibly and other people a lot about
you but it doesn't it's fun it's not as
deep and and hardcore as like who am i
but really that is the question you're
answering and so finding fun ways to
play with like how do you want to answer
Who am I
maybe you're someone who likes taking
taking quizzes and you're more with like
you there's an infinite ways to know who
you are
there's your astrological sign and even
that how many astrological signs are
there right there's I mean there's 12
you also that but I mean like there's
the first nations ones there's the
Nordic ones there's the Indian ones and
of course the the Chinese ones so
for the Lunar New Year and such and like
well do I believe that those things
actually impact my life not very much
but other people might want to know if
I'm I I'm uh oh my I always thought no
not kids a dragon not the point a ram
like a double Rams like a Capricorn and
I think I'm under the Chinese zodiac um
not the point
finding the ways that you answer Who am
I who and where are my people what is my
purpose and how can I actually which is
Ferb's what should I be doing it brings
me closer to my level of happiness what
makes me feel like I'm contributing in
unique way and what do I need and then
our fifth question we had in yesterday
which is what am I are we ready to let
go of and there is no s-- again central
authority hello exploring brothers
there's no central authority that can
answer those things for you there's no
biblical text that can tell you who you
are
there's no Ron passage they can tell you
who your people are unless you're making
it about your religion right Who I am is
a child of God okay cool
what does that mean what does that
actually mean when I am is a Christian
or Muslim and it's under this umbrella
and I'm only okay with people that are
like that that can be the answer to
those questions and there's nothing
particularly wrong with that it's just
if you're stopping other people right
like and that to me is how I started off
this conversation is that to me part of
the drawback the drawback of most
religions is that they need to be the
only religion there's nothing wrong with
having a belief system that you follow
that enhances your life and you feel
helps your family in your community but
either as an invitation or an imposition
it doesn't work - if you're not this
you're going to hell if you're not this
you're not living right if you're not
this you're not and so finding a way
that is Invitational to every individual
regardless so they're part of one of
those religions or they don't have a
religion or their spiritual or they're
not spiritual what
phil's the same role that religion used
to in does fill without the negative
side and to me the negative side is the
quant the need for others to conform and
therefore if we can figure out how do we
don't need others to conform to our to
our way that is the central tenets
but then the I read because of course
holding that that it becomes its central
tenant and whatever self connection that
if we can help people like part of what
religion is is a sign a set of of how
you can guidelines on how to live your
life that we then we can agree on and
then we impose on everybody else there
inquisitions and violence and he needs
good times good times is there any
religion that has not invoked violence
on a massive scale I don't think so
finding but that wasn't necessarily
individuals right the individual stone
but the overarching thank you
Christianity or you die you're a heathen
or you convert finding path that is all
of ours that is common between them that
doesn't require central tenants to to be
involved because this is and this is my
issue with with all religions and I just
had this conversation with my stepdad
when I was in Edmonton of like if what
would make you not believe in the Bible
nothing absolutely nothing I'm like so
God Himself could come and say actually
Bibles of first they wrote it and I was
not I was not privy to it couldn't be
nope nope wouldn't possibly happen I'm
like I don't how you I don't think you
can fully believe in something unless it
can be disproven to you because if you
can't have it disproven to you then
you're I don't like it to me if there's
a god it had whatever truth is has to be
written inside of us on our soul
something that the outside can't argue
that even and that's the like the
difference in the internal in the
external is if my internal and the
external aren't congruent they're not
the same which really they are if
what I'm being told in prayer and
meditation is different than what my
clergy or my spiritual advisor is
telling me in they've learned which one
do I trust which one is the right one
when this one's coming from me and
whenever God gave me and this one is is
from them in the history it's like if
they're no they should always be in
alignment if it was true not in my
regard and so finding that truth that
commonality that peace of what is
written on my soul and in my DNA can be
the same as other peoples and it can be
different my my path and map to follow
is different than other people's and
it's supposed to be different than other
peoples but the commonality can only be
found together if I'm told something I
can never be told some I've never been
told the new Ten Commandments right is
the closest I'm gonna come to the new 10
commandments is like the five questions
they're not Commandments there is no
thou shalt not thou shalt know who you
are
thou shalt know who your people are it's
like it's like recommendation following
the path towards knowing who you are
finding your people finding your purpose
in the moments and overall finding what
you need truly need is it a want is it a
need how do we how do we support more
and more of us having more and more of
our needs met and then more recently
what is what am I willing to let go of
in all of those what am i holding to
strongly to now that I figured out whom
I am am I making like now that I think
you're not I'm queer am I making myself
clear
Mabini Jubilee or my being a queer
Jubilee and it's okay either way am I
willing to let go of this piece right am
i willing to let go of that label nope
am I willing to let go of this piece of
that label that doesn't serve me yeah
and so a constant and stream of these
four now five questions is to me
these choose your own religion because
there's nothing in there that says you
can't do that with with God
and whatever your God is or by yourself
it's only the individual right if you're
like well no no no no no I can't
possibly do that unless it's only
Christians doing that I can't possibly
do that unless it's only Hindus doing
that then that's definitely within you
that issue arose other Hindus other
Christians other atheists and
pastafarians can't all have looked for
the word because they can't remember
what the Flying Spaghetti Monster
congregation is called the individuals
inner is called pastafarians finding the
commonality that can bring us together
and answer these questions because it's
also like I could be in a group of
people with with people that that call
themselves different religions right I
have no problem being in a group of
people who are Hindu and Muslim and
Christian and even Scientologists who if
they're truly there to answer these
questions for themselves and not
inflicting like the only way you can
know who you are is through God by God
the only way you can find your people is
at church on Sunday because they all
found God and that is the only way and
why would you start people they're gonna
be in heaven with you after because none
of that has been proven to me and that
is kind of the point it's like if it
can't be disproven to you it can't be
proven to me and it can't be disproved
like yeah this is the who am i who and
where are my people what is my purpose
what do I need and what am I ready to
let go of and what I'm trying to was
trying to look up before this this and
did not succeed in is there's this
documentary called happy and in it they
go through and there's also a course
because I want to look at the course in
what makes people happy and this is
actually the list I think of what makes
people happy although I wasn't able to
find the list that I had wasn't able to
correlate the two or see if it includes
everything on it but it's do you have a
sense of purpose do you feel like what
you do matters do you have
people in your life who know you and
like you do you have connection and
community do you know who you are and
feel like you matter and you're
important and then there is a certain
routes to your basic needs being met
right it's kind of hard to be overall
happy if you don't have food on the
table if your friends and family are
dying from diseases that are preventable
and curable and you don't have access to
health care it's hard to be happy so
like there is a bear I think it's in
America and probably Canada $60,000 a
year of which up to that point your
happiness does increase and at that
point it does not increase because now
you have your needs met and it's just
stuff on top of that it's just feeling
better than other people and really
better than other people is not on the
list of things that make us happy so I
guess if happiness is our religion true
happiness not happiness that's forced in
the moment because my my sense of
happiness definitely yes but up and down
process there's there's grief there's
anger there's fear but overall there's a
sense of peace and purpose and love for
myself and others and that is a like a
there's a happiness and a joy there that
although not every moment is full of it
it permeates every moment the knowledge
that it exists and even if it doesn't
exist in this moment it is going to
exist it's not holding on to it right
holding on to happiness the word is way
to hold on to happiness because it's
just those things right it's not a
momentary feeling it's am I connected to
people do I have purpose do I know who I
am and feel like I am I'm more the
individual and we again I can't hand it
to somebody else
I can't all the time you're worthy you
are a genius you are the best you
there's ever ever been or ever ever will
be but no one can actually receive that
until they're ready right you have to
actually receive it from the inside it
has to be something that comes from
inside it's like oh look at me all
worthy oh my I'm as good as other repo
oh I do I do have purpose even if I
don't know what it is because I like I
can see people's purpose I can see that
every
this planet matters because of how we
fit together and how when we fit
together in even the smallest ways we
bring profound change to this planet and
to our cultures and ourselves and
there's no faking this like there's no
I'm sure there is but it doesn't
you can't fake happiness right like you
either are you aren't if you're faking
it in fact it's even worse faking happy
are some of the most miserable people
you know whether you're happy or not you
know whether you're connected or not and
so that can't be faked right like the
actual internal I'm I Know Who I am
because you never feel like you get far
enough along the path that you realize
you can't ever fully know who you are it
is a lifelong process but in an
exploring it it's the meaning of life
who are my people
lifelong process I didn't get handed
them day 1 of my life like we used to a
few hundred years ago this is our tribe
these are our people the earth like my
extended family live and die together
fit in or you get ostracized and you die
like this is our option now we can find
our people the people you were born to
aren't probably aren't your people those
are the ones you were born to they're
some of your people but they're not the
same as those that don't share your
genetics but share your purpose share
your genius share your project sure
they're different they're different
groups of people you like me coming on
for an hour and rambly we know what else
is joy to be is rather ridiculous so I'm
gonna try to keep the ones that know
when joins me on to half an hour
tomorrow today I was out to be honest to
go grocery shopping and I did not feel
up to a grocery shopping so I didn't so
I did one today I don't know when I'm
gonna be grocery shopping but tomorrow
is the life coaching session I'm doing
on Fridays so if anybody would like to
do that I will post it later today and
with the link mmm that's not gonna work
we push the randomly show up if you
contact me and you want to be one of the
people on camera
I won't coach whoever
whoever's the first people on camera at
8:30 tomorrow morning whoever's here I
will I will coach we're gonna do a group
coaching session and we're gonna focus
on one of the three tools that kind of
answer these questions because it turns
out there are three of the coaching
things in the coaching book that that
was that partially answer these
questions there's one that is a
relationship to self which again helps
answers the question who am i again none
of these questions are actually
answerable they're just deeper levels
there's one about relationship with
others so that's kind of where my people
how do I get along with other people how
do I find people who are relationship
with others and then there's one about
life's purpose like what is my life's
purpose so all three of those I want to
do over the next three weeks I don't
know if all of them can be done in a
group coaching session but I will be
coaching myself in them if nobody shows
up and if people do show up we will be
coach I'll be coaching whoever shows up
between one and five people because I've
gotta be on camera so we're gonna figure
it out as we go we're gonna do that for
about 8:30 in the morning on Saturday I
do the what I did that week the wrap-up
because I can only come on for 20
minutes because I have our our meeting
after yes yeah our mastermind Saturday
morning project
ambi project meeting I'm in the process
thanks to Nick who pointed out that I
need he's like you need a website that
says what you're up to if it's something
because he didn't say looking but I was
like I know I can't do a website unless
the Wix website and then it's not Google
it's not helpful it's like already like
a Google Doc it's like a Google Doc I
can do not I can do is someone working
on a Google Doc that I can put in the
description of all of the YouTube videos
for all of the various things that I'm
up to and what I'm doing and - so other
people can kind of get it and get across
with it and how people can get involved
with each one Facebook group reach
there's its own social media for each
somewhat and there's different people
involved in different ones so I'm gonna
go go get ready for my other
conversation that's happening in 45
minutes which I love and I will see you
oh it's worth 420 no wait tours coach
you in for an hour